One Step Wrong turns digital judgment into a practiceable skill.
An educator starts with a school and public official guidance.
Every retained fact keeps its source, confidence, review state, and explicit unknowns.
The educator approves the profile before it can influence a rehearsal.
The Scenario Architect compiles a validated world, bounded cast, explicit actions, and deterministic endings.
The learner enters an ordinary reimbursement task under realistic deadline pressure.
Free-form dialogue changes the people and pressure, but it cannot change canonical state.
Only explicit controls verify identity, pause payment, and produce the deterministic safe ending.
Replay starts with fresh conversational and canonical state.
When unsafe actions affect payment and access, only the relevant recovery steps become required.
The debrief reconstructs the demonstrated trace without inventing events.
This reliable take uses reviewed fixtures. Live GPT-5.6 paths use the same validated boundaries.